Chanoon Na

Greater Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada

chanoonna@gmail.com

+1 778-917-0180



linkedin.com/in/chanoon-na-2482a6208

Summary

Web developer with 2 years of total experience in SaaS industry.

Experienced in Frontend development with Typescript, React and Redux.

Built complex feature using graph data structure requires various crud actions as a feature lead.

Experience

Frontend Developer

Mosaic

Feb 2023 - Present (2 months)

Feature lead Frontend developer

Mosaic

Apr 2021 - Feb 2023 (1 year 11 months)

Responsibilities as a feature lead

- Manage and report feature development tasks for successful feature development
- Manage collaboration with design and BE team
- Frontend development

Responsibilities outside of main role

- Tasks management: Prioritizing, assigning and estimating on dev cost
- Relief tech dept: Writing tests for old code, refactoring inefficient code and performance optimization
- PR review

Education

Lighthouse Labs

Jan 2021 - Mar 2021

Andong National University

Bachelor of Laws - LLB 2001 - 2008

Skills

Ruby on Rails • Task Management • React.js • TypeScript • JavaScript • Ruby • Redux.js • C++ Webpack
Haskell